Ist was?
Nene.
Verstehst du etwas nicht?
Nein, alles gut.
Du musst mich schon fragen, wenn du was nicht verstehst.
Zeig schon.
Ach, da?
Wenn du x = 5 setzt, ist 25 + 5a = 30.
Oh nein, ich fühle ihre Brüste...
Also, was kommt dann raus?
82? Nein, 83.
Hä?
Nichts!
Kei-chan?
Alles okay, Kei-chan?
Au...
Doki Fansubs
Translator:        tony-san
TLC:        Niphty
Timer:    masat
Editor:    Parkur
Typesetter: Holo
Karaoke: Jecht
Karaoke Timer: Holo
Songs TL: Niphty, tony-san, Holo
Encoder: kokus
QC: Niphty, milkmandan, nt, Holo
http://doki.hologfx.com/
#doki@irc.rizon.net
This is a free fansub.
Not for sale, rent or Ebay.
Private Nachhilfe
Was soll das denn?
Gib dir mehr Mühe!
Deine Chance zu bestehen liegt nur bei 50%?
Das ist wie Glücksspiel.
Damit hätte man rechnen müssen.
Wie kannst du das nur mit Glücksspiel vergleichen?
Ich weiß, das ist schlecht.
Aber ich konnte mich beim Lernen nie konzentrieren.
Das kann ich verstehen.
Hör auf ihm zuzustimmen!
Reiß dich gefälligst zusammen, sonst können wir nicht auf die gleiche Schule gehen!
Du hast ja recht...
Ich will nicht, dass das passiert!
There are lots of things I want to do with you in high school!
Work hard! There's still time.
Ako-nee.
Don't worry! Starting from today I will study with you until the end.
Eh?
I will be your tutor!
You want to become my tutor?
Yeah!
Hey, wait a minute.
Having him all to yourself, that's so unfair!
But if it's Riko...
I've passed too.
By rolling a pencil around, right?
Alright! The answer is 3.
Hey, you there!
Yes!
I'm not going to say that you can't do that, but roll your pencil a bit more quietly.
It won't be by luck! I will definitely make sure Kei-chan passes.
Definitely...?
Don't worry!
Just leave it to your sister.
Ow...
Really... What are you doing?
You can't get distracted.
I know that, but...
Why are you dressed like that?
I'm a tutor.
It's more interesting this way.
Maybe it is...
Could it be that you... like this kind of cosplay?
No!
No?
It's just that you're giving off a different aura than usual... So I...
Want to see it?
You can't yet.
Right now you have to focus and study.
Ako-nee.
I will work hard too!
I got it! I'll study hard and I won't get distracted!
That's the spirit! Kei-chan.
Listen carefully, to solve this problem...
Hey, you're looking at me again.
Damn it, I won't lose.
Did your studies go well?
Sort of...
Don't worry, I was with him.
Ako's grades have always been excellent.
I believe in you.
I'm not good at studying anyway...
You're just like me.
Not blood-related, right?
Eh? Maybe the fact that I'm not good at studying is genetic.
It's not something to laugh about.
Oh yeah, Kei-chan, what do you want for a midnight snack?
Anything is fine.
Then how about Oyakodon?
Oyakodon? Keita is so brave!
Though, you can't borrow your mum.
My, what a shame.
I didn't mean it like that...
I want to take care of Keita too.
Even if you say that... You can't tutor him...
You can't cook, so a midnight snack is out of the question.
I can still take care of my little brother.
That was good! Riko.
I love this type of rivalry!
If you're talking about taking care of him, I can do that too!
My, if it's like this, there won't even be room left for me.
Isn't sibling love great?
I don't know what to say to them.
Because the interior angles in a triangle add up to 180 degrees.
So the isosceles triangle...
Kei-chan, are you listening?
Isn't it just triangle relationships? I'm listening.
Isn't it only 2 o'clock?
It's already 2 a.m. Normally I'd be...
Hey, open your eyes.
Well, if it's like this...
Kei-chan!
So? Are you awake now?
A-Ako-nee...
Let's work hard for a bit more.
Y-Yeah.
Maths Quiz
I studied this with Ako-nee yesterday.
I think I solve this by...
Not that!
No good... I can't remember it.
So, it was a complete failure?
Sorry.
You don't remember anything?
No... I still remembered but...
Um... Breasts...
I see...
Sorry.
It's not your fault. It's because I didn't teach you properly...
It's not your fault either!
Alright! Change of plans!
You're not in a suit today?
This is a special lesson.
Special?
Then, let us start.
W-What is this?
Don't you remember a lot about breasts and legs?
If I do it like this, you won't forget what I teach you.
So... all over your body is...
Of course. My right breast says "be interested in."
And it means?
To have interest?
That's right! Just like this.
The inside of my left leg says "look at."
It means to look.
I'm looking.
The inside of my right leg says...
..."be glad to."
It means to happily do something.
"At... last."
It means?
At last!
S-Sorry.
I-It's fine, be sure to remember it.
Good morning.
Look at something: "Look at."
Happily do something: "be glad to."
To have interest...
I think, be...
"Be interested in."
To have... interest...
S-Sorry.
Molester!
A wild beast!
Keita is actually...
That's wrong! I was only...
That's mean, Keita-senpai!
Even if you aren't a molester, I would gladly...
"A" cup of tea!
Conditioned
Reflex
So, there were no problems in English?
The test was fine,
but a lot of other terrible things happened.
Our top priority right now is to get your grades up!
So...
Today's lesson is History.
In the year 794, the peace in....
I can't! This is too embarrassing.
Happy Midnight Cooking
Even if it's me...
If it's for Keita...
Strawberry panties?!
What's going on, Keita?
There has to be something wrong, since you got an 85.
Did you cheat?
Of course not!
If you didn't cheat, then how did you get such a high score?
I didn't do anything special.
I just asked Ako-nee to be my tutor.
Tutor?!
That bright mind...
The amazing student council president?
Is it the Ako-senpai we've always admired?
Y-Yeah...
Hey, tell us, how good was the private lesson?
I'm sure she taught you something other than school work.
We really want her to become a teacher!
Ako-nee, I don't really understand this part.
Where?
You see... I've always...
It's fine, if it's Kei-chan.
I will teach you anything.
Ako-nee!
Kei-chan!
Ah~
Such heavenly bliss!
You did it right?
Who did what to whom?
Then what sort of studying did you do?
What kind...
Nothing special.
I knew you did perverted things with your sister!
I didn't!
Home Economics Room
I can't damage the outer skin.
My, how amazing... she's self-studying.
Next is cucumbers.
First get rid of the spikes on the outside.
And after sprinkling it with salt, rub it around on the chopping board.
Rub-bing?
Rubbing, rubbing.
Rolling on the chopping board, it's alright, it won't hurt~
Softly rolling.
Is this how it feels?
I rub...
I rub... rub, rub, rub, rub, rub...
Wha-
What is that girl doing!?
You should be ready with History now, right?
Yeah.
Then think of this as a reward for working hard.
I will definitely show you.
Today, I will teach you everything about girls.
But, we're...
Did you feel it?
A-Ako-nee.
Right now, I'm your teacher.
Tea-cher...
Work hard... Using my body.
What kind of dream was that?!
It's rare that Ako-nee worked up the nerve to teach me...
What am I thinking?!
Sorry, Ako-nee.
What did I do?
W-What are you doing?
Sleeping with you.
I wasn't referring to that.
Why are you here...
Originally, I came over to help you study.
But you were asleep.
So, when did you come?
About ten minutes ago?
Then you didn't wake me up,
and happily slept next to me?
What's wrong with that?
Forget about that. Study, study!
Don't change the subject.
Alright, I'll test you today.
Eh?
You don't have to be so surprised.
I've already been tested in school.
You can't be satisfied with that!
There's another mock exam this weekend, right?
You have to work harder!
But there's no need for a test at home...
I see...
Then I'll reward you if you answer it right!
I'll give you a kiss.
What are you saying?
Isn't that more of a punishment game?
That's right... A punishment game.
Um...
I understand.
In that case, I'll have to make it more like a punishment game, eh?
No... It's already...
Calm down... Calm down.
Ako-nee!
Ten questions!
For every one you get wrong, as punishment, you have to kiss me!
That's ridiculous.
How could I do something like that?
That's why this is called a punishment game!
That's not what you should call it!
If you don't like it, you better answer as though your life depended on it!
Here we go! First question.
What year was the Tokugawa Shogunate defeated?
Um... 1867?
What year was the Muromachi Shogunate defeated?
1573.
What year was the Kamakura Shogunate defeated?
1333.
Uh? He's doing alright.
I actually remembered?
Alright, next question!
Who was the last general of Muromachi Shogunate?
Huh?
Tick, tock, tick, tock... Ding!
The correct answer is Ashikaga Yoshiaki.
That's not a year!
This is the punishment of the punishment game.
I said I was sorry...
But, I forgive you.
For you to give me a kiss by yourself...
I haven't had one since 4th grade.
It's making me a bit nervous.
W-What, a bit nervous...
Something like this...
I can't do it...
I-Idiot! Why am I getting nervous too?
Standing in front of me is my sister!
I can't... hold it in anymore.
Don't make me wait too long... Kei-chan.
Oh yeah... This is a punishment game.
As it's a punishment game, it can't be helped.
Because it's a punishment game...
Please... Hurry...
W-Wait.
Kei-chan you can't!
If it leaves a mark... It'll be troublesome.
But if it's a place that can't be seen... then it's fine.
Ako-nee.
Oh well.
It's just a punishment game.
Alright, that's enough.
Ow...
Riko!
What subject are you studying?
Did you think I wouldn't show up?
Sorry!
Disregarded.
Listen to me... Riko-nee.
This is just a punishment game.
Eh? What is this?
A midnight snack.
I made it for you.
You made it?
Could it be?
Riko-nee...
Even though I don't know if it's going to taste good...
If you don't mind...
Of course I'll eat it.
Keita!
Thank you! Thanks for the food!
Wait a minute.
My, my...
That's why I said to let me take care of Kei-chan.
I'm home!
Welcome back, Kei-chan.
I made it! My grade went up, look!
Congratulations, Kei-chan.
This is all thanks to you.
Thank you.
Isn't this great? Kei-chan.
Alluring Sweets!
Girls are like desserts.
Granulated sugar and spices.
The condiments combine little by little when least expected.
This isn't a kiss.
Sweet... Please taste some of my chocolates.
Next time...
Alluring sweets. I'll give you a kiss.