Der Sommer ist vorbei. Die Blätter fallen ab.
Die Zeit vergeht so schnell...
Ziel: Tamahide Hochschule!
Mir bleibt nicht mehr viel Zeit.
Diesen Winter wird sich entscheiden ob ich am Ende lache oder weine.
Okay! Los geht's!
Kei-chan, Abendessen ist fertig!
Darum fange ich bestimmt wieder den größten Tunfisch!
Wie läuft es mit dem Lernen?
Geht...
Du bist ganz schön nachlässig.
Warum lässt du dich nicht wieder von Ako unterrichten?
Das ist nicht nötig!
Und wenn ich-
Was kannst du ihm schon beibringen?
Du solltest ihre Hilfe annehmen.
Das ist ja das Problem...
Ach Keita, hast du eigentlich schon einen Glücksbringer?
Glücksbringer?
Na für die Prüfungen. Like for Dazaifu.
Dazaifu? Sounds great!
I'll visit the hot springs with your mother and bring one along on the side!
On the side?
But as an exam applicant, you need one, right?
There are exam applicants all over the country, you know?
As if God has the time to tend to every one of them.
But if it was a unique charm just for me, I'd be okay with that.
Gammel Sami
github.com/GammelSami/kissxsissubs
This is a free fansub.
Not for sale, rent or Ebay.
Turn to God in Times of Suffering
OK!
OK! Let's do this!
Doing your best, aren't you?
It's the home stretch after all! I won't let myself get distracted while studying!
I'll make some tea for you then.
Thanks.
Keita, wear this.
A headband?
I made it. It's a special divine headband for success, just for you.
Headband: Certain victory
Thank you!
How is it?
Yeah, I feel hyped up already! It works.
That's great!
OK, let's try hard. Thanks, Riko-nee!
Ah, Kei-chan.
Damn, she beat me to it.
The headband does make a difference. It really is a must for exam applicants.
Give it your best shot, Keita.
I sure will, for your sake as well!
Kei-chan, a late-night snack!
This rocks. It's Katsudon!
Katsu means "to win"
Katsu for winning. Overused, but still.
Ako, you...
Now it's my turn.
I'm digging in!
It's delicious!
You're eating like you haven't had any dinner.
That's because it's really good! Ako-nee's late-night snacks are the best!
Tomorrow it'll be a cutlet sandwich.
Great!
I'll cook special meals for you until the exam, so look forward to it!
I get the feeling I'm going to pass with flying colours!
That's great!
Thanks for the meal.
It was my pleasure.
It was delicious.
There's an apple for dessert.
Pun on "appu" = up and "appuru" = apple
Knowledge up-pple or something.
Ako-nee, it was delicious.
What?
Ouch!
Riko-nee, what are you doing?
I know I can only make headbands.
What's this about? I'm not letting you kick me like this.
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You're still just a kid if you're getting serious over this.
You're the kid for starting!
What about me is kid-like?
Your height!
Judging by appearance...
I'm sorry, did I hurt you?
Riko-nee?
Are you okay, Riko-nee?
Geez, that's not good.
As I said, I'm sorry.
You did it on purpose.
W-What?
We were just fooling around, but you like it better that way, don't you?
Like I said, what?
Surely, you know where your foot hit me.
Say it. Where is this?
Th-There.
I won't know with just "there".
Tell me precisely.
I won't!
You're to blame, just so you know.
Riko-nee! Hey!
No. I'll teach you that I'm not a kid.
How am I going to...
...understand like this? Just wait.
We saw each other naked in the bathtub, too.
We didn't see each other. That was more like an accident.
You already accidentally saw my pussy.
Don't say pussy!
But I do remember, the feeling of your hand hitting me there.
Clearly, even now...
I'm getting turned on...
My panties are going to get dirty.
Riko-nee, what are you doing with my foot?
I came. Incredible.
Stop it already!
Moisture?
Can you tell? Can you feel me soaking your feet?
Soa...
I'm sorry, but, it won't stop.
Your foot is quite big.
I might like your foot better than your hand.
Riko-nee looks kind of cute.
Don't stare at me like that.
Isn't this your fault? There's no way I can take my eyes off you.
It's okay, keep watching. Or rather, I want you to watch.
Is it disgraceful for a sister to get off on her little brother's foot?
Yeah, doing this is totally disgraceful.
Sorry, was that too strong?
That... felt really good.
I might be ruined for marriage.
At least say you'll take responsibility.
Well...
You don't want to? Or do you think it's a joke?
You can't  joke about things like this.
Riko-nee...
Kei-chan, sorry for the wait!
Uh, what's the matter?
Erm, no, nothing.
It's nothing.
Oh, Riko, your face is really red.
Maybe it's getting hot in here.
Then why don't you get out of the kotatsu?
kotatsu = table with heater
Kei-chan, you're sweating, too!
Yeah, it's hot, I'll just...
...stay here.
What's going on?
To be honest, I can't.
Keita, are you...
You're not going to eat your apples?
I... I'll eat them!
What's wrong?
No...
Riko-nee, why now you idiot?
As I thought, I got Keita big. I'm so happy!
These are just thin sweatpants so I can feel her toes...
Keita, you're not only getting big, but also hot and ready to burst...
I can feel it...
What is going on here?
What the hell are you two doing?!
What are you doing, keeping Keita from studying all the time? What will you do if he fails?
I'll take responsibility and care for him?
Are you going to make him your gigolo?
Stop fooling around. At least try to help Kei-chan pass the...
Where did all these people come from?
It's really not long until the exams.
Hey, it's Toda.
Ako-senpai, Riko-senpai!
Are you here to pray for your exams too?
Well, at this point, begging the gods is my only chance.
I still have three to go, here! Look!
Wow, what a collection.
Yeah, it's strength in numbers, after all.
Hey, I have to go, bye!
This is bad. Even if we get that many victory headbands, we don't know if it'll work.
Even if you say that, we don't have time to accumulate that many!
Then it's a battle between numbers and quality!
Charm
How's it going?
What're you here for?
You doing this alone worries me.
You're probably looking up unnecessary things.
I'm not!
Oh, there's something that looks good.
Erm, "It's been said to have an effect on competitions like exams and gambling."
A wife or lover's pubic hair as a charm
A wife or lover's pubic hair as a
pubic hair
P-
Pubic hair.
Ako, is yours growing?
Yes, it is growing!
That Riko... What is she asking me in a place like that?
Ah, that was embarrassing.
And that remark, to top it off!
I'm sure you can still count them.
There's no way I can still count them.
No way...
No way... right...?
1, 2, 3...
Phew, so refreshing!
Riko.
What?
I counted them!
I didn't think you'd really count them.
But, but!
You know that I'm very sparse, too.
I just played on the fact that as twins, we're probably quite similar.
But, but!
If you're going to be so concerned about it, then show me.
How is it?
Don't laugh like that!
Sorry, sorry. I just thought that it's funny that we twins are similar to that level.
But isn't it great that you won't have to worry alone?
Riko!
Ako!
It's great that we were born as twins!
So noisy...
So that's that.
Now that I've calmed down, a greater problem arises.
What?
Do you think this poorly made charm will be effective?
Don't worry, if you combine it with mine, I'm sure it'll be more powerful.
Since when are we doing this together?
Now now, think about it.
If we give Keita two charms he doesn't need, what do you think he'll do?
He might throw them away.
Right?
Well, I'll leave the sewing of the pouch to you then.
Damn it.
And while we're at it, why not make Keita pluck them?
Make K-Kei-chan pluck them?
Kei-chan, this is embarrassing.
Now, step out of them.
N-No.
Then you want to quit?
No.
It's okay, Kei-chan.
I'll start.
It hurts, Kei-chan!
I can't help it. There's only two or three for me to pluck anyway.
Stop it!
Even if you say that...
Please, make it just one.
I don't have that many. I'm going to look like an infant!
What are you saying?
You pretty much look like an infant right now.
You stupid... Kei-chan you...
I'm sorry, my hand slipped.
What's all this about?
Don't ask me!
I'm doing it, Ako-nee!
I pulled one out.
Yeah, that hurt.
It hurt that bad?
No, I'm fine.
Ako-nee, as a thanks and sorry, I'll lick it for you.
Wait!
Wait, no!
I said I'm all right!
No, your mouth is...
Kei-chan, I said no!
She returns at last.
Say Ako, aren't you getting really perverted lately?
No way. I'm not like you!
I've been fully perverted from the start.
Really...?
Hm, as it's this late already, we have to do it quickly.
Well then, I'm going to the bathroom.
Since you just took a bath, why not put a clean one into it?
Or is the pee going to be an upgrade?
Of course not! I'm going there to pull one out!
That statement seems dubious.
Do you think I can do something that embarrassing in front of someone?
Now then...
Keita.
Kei-chan.
I'm back.
Welcome back.
Did you pull one out?
Stop saying it in such an embarrassing way!
With this, the ingredients are complete.
The truth is, I have something I really need to reflect on.
What's this all of a sudden?
Up until now, I've thought that old men with really sparse hair who go to great lengths to maintain it were incredibly lame.
I was wrong.
I now know that each and every one of them is extremely important.
I apologize, old men!
Ako, just go to bed now.
Pass
It's done!
What kind of humiliating thing have we made?
I completely missed the timing to go back on this.
Let's make it clear that the contents of this charm will stay a secret between the two of us.
In this, you and I are enmeshed.
A charm, for me?
But I don't really...
It's fine!
Just take it!
Thanks. But where did you get it?
It's handmade.
Oh, really?
Let's see...
Stop!
What is it?
This charm has one thing you have to be careful about!
We would like you to keep it as close to you as possible!
But...
If you open it, you're going down.
You're going down for real.
Never open it, ever!
I understand. I'll never open it.
What is this about? What did they give me?
This is a charm, right?
Kei-chan!
Keita!
But with my sisters' vigour... this'll be effective for sure!
I got it, I promise.
Thank you, Ako-nee, Riko-nee.
Please give me the ability to pass! I beg you, I beg you!
I'm off!
Hey Kei-chan, what about the charm?
I put it on, see!
Now I can show it to the world.
In a place...
...this open!
Am I imagining this or is there a breeze picking up?
The breeze was there all along.
Screw this, we shouldn't have done this!
Isn't this what they call imprudence?
No, it's not!
At Last, the Real Thing!
Keita came down with a high fever just before the important exams.
I'll do anything to make him healthy again!
Now, relax.
This is therapy. The-ra-py!
Next episode: At Last, the Real Thing!
I'll give you a kiss!